https://www.tinytalk.co.uk/privacy.php

JOIN THE TEAM
FIND OUT MOREFIND A CLASSNEWBORNSABOUT USAWARDSPARTNERSWHAT OTHERS SAY!
FOLLOW USBLOGNEWSLETTERFACEBOOKTWITTERINSTAGRAMYOUTUBE
TRAININGBECOME A TEACHERCHILDCARE TRAINING
CONTACT USPHONEEMAIL USWRITE TO USPRIVACY
FIND A CLASS NEAR YOU:
GO!
Type in a postcode or town and then choose a result from the dropdown menu.
TinyTalk Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice and Data Protection Policy
TinyTalk takes privacy and data protection very seriously, following strict rules on keeping data to ensure that they meet GDPR regulations and the Data Protection Act.
This information sets out how TinyTalk uses and protects information that is given to them, for example when products are purchased from the online shop, families attend classes or people make enquiries to TinyTalk.
Overview
TinyTalk will look after any personal information that is shared with them.
TinyTalk will ensure that personal information is only used if an individual has previously told us that they are happy for us to do so. If a person wishes to opt out of being contacted, TinyTalk will make it very easy and will never release information to organisations outside TinyTalk for their marketing purposes.
Personal Data
TinyTalk collects information about individuals when they register/attend Tiny Talk classes or place an order for products through the online shop.
Any personal information provided via the website or Enrolment Forms for classes, such as names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses, will not be sold on for any marketing purposes.
Personal data collected for one purpose is not subsequently used for another without the individual’s consent.
How Data is Used
Information is collected, for example from attendance at classes or when orders are processed. If someone has agreed to be contacted TinyTalk may, periodically, send promotional emails such as newsletters, information on new products, classes and other TinyTalk opportunities and developments.
TinyTalk uses Mailchimp to send some information out. For further information on Mailchimp: privacy@mailchimp.com or their website: https://mailchimp.com/
Mailchimp accounts can be terminated, directly through Mailchimp, or via TinyTalk.
Security
TinyTalk takes all reasonable care to safeguard personal information through security policies and secure business processes; it is committed to ensuring information is secure.
TinyTalk uses two IT Management Services who have access to the Head Office computers for administrative purposes. The TinyTalk systems are secure and password –protected. All data is stored within the EU.
TinyTalk has implemented appropriate physical, technical and organisational measures to protect personal information. Great care is taken to ensure that data cannot be accessed or viewed by anyone not authorised to do so.
TinyTalk only keeps your information as long as is reasonable and necessary. Only relevant and necessary information is stored. TinyTalk carries out regular administration of files and records to remove duplicated materials and irrelevant information.
Any debit or credit card details received on the website are passed securely to Sage Pay, the payment processing partner.
TinyTalk is exempt from registering with the Information Commissioner’s Office for the following three reasons:
•	It is an educational company.
•	The information is always kept in-house and NEVER sold on.
•	TinyTalk only uses the information for company news, developments or with details of future events.
Request for Information
If you would like a copy of the information held about you, please email or write to TinyTalk, with ID, to:
TinyTalk
Unit 3, The Dairy,
Tilehouse Farm Offices,
East Shalford Lane,
Guildford,
Surrey,
GU4 8AE
info@tinytalk.co.uk
It is important that personal information is accurate and up-to-date.
If you believe it to be inaccurate or out-of-date, please inform TinyTalk.
Changes to our Privacy Notice
TinyTalk keeps their privacy notice under regular review and will place any updates on this page.
This privacy notice has been compiled in March 2018.
Receive our newsletter!
Receive our newsletter!
Name:
Email:
Send
Thank you!
We will get back to you soon...
IMPORTANT!
Please check yourSPAM/ JUNK / PROMOTIONS folders - in case our reply to you ends up in one.
This site uses cookies to improve your browsing experience. CLICK HERE to accept the use of cookies > close
